Guide to the International Convention records 1908-2006 IBT0019
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
International Convention records
1906-2011
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
International Brotherhood of Teamsters
International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America
IBT0019
10 Linear Feet
This collection is comprised of materials produced by the International Brotherhood of Teamsters' International Conventions dating from 1906-2011. The materials include organizational logistics, convention programs, delegate lists, material produced by Convention committees, transcripts of speeches, proceedings for each convention, proposed and adopted Constitutions, and reports.
Arrangement
Organized into two series: Convention Organization and Logistics material and Convention Publications
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Scope and Contents
This collection is comprised of materials produced by the International Brotherhood of Teamsters' International Conventions dating from 1906-2011. The materials include organizational logistics, convention programs, delegate lists, material produced by Convention committees, transcripts of speeches, proceedings for each convention, proposed and adopted Constitutions, and reports.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred by the International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 2012 January 4 [2012.003].
Biographical / Historical
The International Convention is considered to be the highest deliberative body of the IBT. From its founding in 1903 to 1912 the International Convention was held annually. From 1912 to 1915 it was held every three years. From 1915 to date it is held every five years. Conventions usually run five days during which officers are nominated, committees report out, invited speakers speak and resolutions are passed.
Material on loan
Labor and laboring classes; Labor; Labor unions; Labor unions -- United States -- History -- 20th century
- Convention Organization and Logistics material, 1969-1982; Series 1; 3.5 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series comprised of materials produced by the Teamsters' many International Conventions. Included so far are materials from the 20th, 21st and 22nd Conventions, dating from 1969-1982. The materials vary widely in content, including organizational logistics, convention programs, delegate lists, material produced by Convention committees, and transcripts of various speeches.
  Arrangement
  Series is arranged roughly chronologically, following the original order of materials covering the Teamsters' International Conventions.
  - 5th Convention, Credential to Convention, August 5, 1907; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - 20th Convention Call, 1971 March 10 - April 22; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Convention Hall, 1969 August 20 - 1971 June 30; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Convention Hall: Show, 1971 February 17 - July 22; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Court Reporter, 1970 June 27 - 1971 May 7; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Delegates, 1971 March 25 - June 21; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Delinquent Locals, 1971 March 10 - May 27; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Entertainment, 1971 April 28; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Exhibits, 1970 August 12 - 1971 June 17; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Hotel Arrangements, 1970 February 17 - 1971 June 11; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Instructions to Affiliates, 1970 July 6 - 1971 June 11; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Meeting Schedule, 1971; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1971 May 5 - June 16; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Nominations and Election Procedure, 1971 July 8; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Office Facilities, 1970 October 10 - 1971 July 2; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Officers, Auditors, and Organizers, 1971 May 19 - July 1; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Press Arrangements, 1971 June 15 - July 4; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Press Releases, 1971 April 2 - July 1; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Program, 1971 July 5-10; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Purchase Orders, 1971 February 10 - June 10; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Souvenir Information, 1970 May 19 - 1971 May 28; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Special Events, 1971 June 2-22; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Staff Arrangements, 1971 March 12 - July 21; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Thomas E. Flynn, 1971 May 10 - July 8; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Transportation Arrangements, undated; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - 1966 Convention Material, undated; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Committees: General, 1971 June 10 - July 6; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Appeals and Grievances Committee, 1971 May 25 - June 29; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Arrangements Committee, 1970 April 9 - 1971 May 21; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Constitution Committee, 1969 November 7 - 1971 June 10; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Credentials Committee, 1971 March 19 - June 17; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Officers Report Committee, 1971 May 24-25; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Reading Clerk, 1971 May 26 - July 1; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Resolutions Commitee, 1971 May 25 - June 29; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Rules Committee, 1971 May 24 - June 17; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Sergeant-at-Arms, 1971 May 25 - July 7; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Guest Information [1/3], 1971 June 4 - August 10; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Guest Information [2/3], 1971 June 10-15; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Guest Information [3/3], 1971 March 15 - June 15; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - 21st Convention General Arrangements, 1976 March 2 - April 8; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Attorneys, 1976 May 24; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Convention Call, 1976 March; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Convention Center, 1976 February 27 - March 10; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Convention Office, 1976 February 26 - April 3; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Court Reporters, 1975 January 6 - 1976 January 6; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Delegates and Alternates, 1975 June 24 - 1976 May 18; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Delinquent Locals, 1976 February 2 - May 25; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Exhibits, 1976 March 8 - May 17; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence, 1975 December 6 - 1976 June; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Greyhound Exposition Services, 1974 November 22 - 1976 April 29; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Hotel Reservation Information, 1975 January 31 - 1976 April 30; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Officers' Report, 1976 March 26; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Press Arrangements, undated; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Program, 1975 October 23 - 1976 May 25; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Retirees, undated; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Souvenir Information, 1974 September 26 - 1976 May 10; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Staff Information [1/2], 1976 April 27 - May 26; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Staff Information [2/2], 1976 May 12-26; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Visitor Information, 1976 March 11 - May 10; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Committees: General, 1976 April 22-26; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Appeals and Grievances Committee, 1976 April 12 - May 26; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Arrangements Committee, 1976 April 12-26; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Constitution Committee, 1976 March 17 - May 6; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Credentials Committee, 1976 April 12-26; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Officers' Report Committee, 1976 April 9-26; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Reading Clerks, 1976 April 12; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Resolutions Committee, 1976 March 22 - May 21; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Rules Committee, 1976 April 9 - May 19; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Sergeant-at-Arms [1/2], 1976 April 26 - June 10; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Sergeant-at-Arms [2/2], 1976 March 11 - May 24; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Guests: General, undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Attorneys, 1976 April 1 - June 3; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Clergy, 1976 May 4-14; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Employer Association Representatives, 1976 May 5 - June 2; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Employers, 1976 May 5 - June 9; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Friends [1/2], 1976 May 5 - June 10; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Friends [2/2], 1976 March 11 - June 7; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Government Officials, 1976 May 5 - June 16; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Las Vegas VIPs, 1976 May 5-24; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Laundry Workers International Union, 1976 May 5 - June 5; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Local Union 732, 1976 April 28 - May 7; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - International Union Officers, 1976 May 5 - June 11; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Retired International Union Officers and Employees, and Wives of Deceased International Union Officers, 1976 May 5 - June 4; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Retired Local Union and Joint Council Officers, 1976 April 8 - June 3; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Speakers, 1976 May 4 - June 10; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - 22nd Convention General Arrangements, 1981 March 23 - May 7; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Balloting, undated; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Convention Call, 1981; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Convention Center, 1977 Januray 17 - 1980 April 1; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Convention Office, 1981 January 22-28; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Delegates and Alternates, 1981 January 19 - June 1; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - General Information, 1981 January 16 - July 9; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Hotel Reservations, 1979 June - 1981 January 28; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - "The International Teamster" Magazine, 1981 July; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - John English Convention Address, 1981 July; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - "Officers' Report to the 22nd International Convention", 1981; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Press Arrangements, 1981 April 13; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Program, 1981; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Ray Schoessling Speeches, 1981 June 1-5; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Souvenir Information, 1980 June 19 - August 21; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Staff Information [1/3], 1981 April 30 - May 9; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Staff Information [2/3], 1981 April 10 - May 12; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Staff Information [3/3], 1981 March 25 - 1982 January 25; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Committees: General, 1981 February 10 - May 27; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Appeals and Grievances Committee, 1981 March 13 - April 7; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Arrangements Committee, 1981 March 13 - May 27; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Constitution Committee [1/2], 1981 March 13 - May 8; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Constitution Committee [2/2], 1981 March 13 - 27; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Credentials Committee, 1981 March 13 - May 28; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Officers' Report Committee, 1981 March 13 - May 13; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - "Proposed Constitution and By-Laws", 1981; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Reading Clerks, 1981 March 13 - April 30; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Resolutions Committee, 1981 March 13 - April 16; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Rules Committee, 1981 March 13 - April 13; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Sergeant-at-Arms [1/3], 1981 March 13 - April 16; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Sergeant-at-Arms [2/3], 1981 March 13 - April 30; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Sergeant-at-Arms [3/3], 1981 March 13 - April 30; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Guest Information: A-D, 1981 May 7-27; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Guest Information: E-K, 1981 February 10 - May 28; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Guest Information: L-P, 1981 May 7 - July 15; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Guest Information: Q-Z, 1981 May 7-14; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Guest Information: Miscellaneous, 1981 January 6 - July 15; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Attorneys, 1981 February 23 - April 9; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Clergy, 1981 March 4 - July 9; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - General [1/2], 1981 April 14 - May 29; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - General [2/2], 1981 January 13 - May 4; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Government Officials, 1981 April 17; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Las Vegas VIPs, 1981 April 27; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Retired International Union Officers and Employees, and Wives of Deceased International Union Officers, 1981 May 7 - September 4; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Retired Local Union and Joint Customs Officers, 1981 May 7; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Speakers, 1981 May 8; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - 100th Anniversary Event Schedule and Notecard Binder, September 8, 2003; Series 1 (Box 20, Item 1)
  - RMT Conference Speech Transcription, 2009; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - "National Days of Action" Pamphlet and Petition to Gary Loveman, CEO of Caesars Entertainment Corp, June 24, 2011; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Seating Arrangement Notes and Section 10 Seating Chart, 2011; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - 28th IBT Convention Ribbons, Agenda, Folder Handouts and 'Convention News' newsletter', June 27-July 1, 2011; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Speech Notes, 2011; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Architectural Print-outs, 2011; Series 1 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Convention Publications, 1906-2006; Series 2; 4.5 Linear Feet
  Series is arranged chronologically by the date of each Convention.
  This series is comprised of material published by the IBT's many Conventions. Represented are materials from the IBT's sixth through twenty-seventh conventions (1908-2006), with material from the eigth convention absent. Included are proceedings for each convention, as well as proposed and adopted Constitutions, several reports, and delegate lists.
  - Proceedings of the First Annual Convention of the United Teamsters of America: Minutes of Morning Session, 1906 August 8-15; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Proceedings of the Third Annual Convention of the United Teamsters of America, 1908 August 3; Series 2 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Sixth Convention Proceedings, 1908 August 3-8; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Seventh Convention Proceedings, 1910 August 1-6; Series 2 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Eighth Convention: Proceedings, October 7-12, 1912; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Ninth Convention Proceedings, 1915 October 4-9; Series 2 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Tenth Convention Proceedings, 1920 October 4-9; Series 2 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Eleventh Convention Proceedings, 1925 September 14-19; Series 2 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Eleventh Convention, Official Program of the Quintennial Convention, 1925 September 14-19; Series 2 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Twelfth Convention Proceedings, 1930 September 8-13; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Thirteenth Convention: Reports of Officers, 1935 September 9; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Fourteenth Convention Proceedings, 1940 September 9-14; Series 2 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Fourteenth Convention: Souvenir, 1940 September 9-14; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Fourteenth Convetion: Daniel J. Tobin Dedication, September 9, 1940; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Fifteenth Convention: List of Credentials on File, 1947 August 11; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Fifteenth Convention: Report of General Secretary-Treasurer & Report of Trustees, August 11, 1947; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Fifteenth Convention, Report of General President Daniel J. Tobin, 1947 August 11; Series 2 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Fifteenth Convention Proceedings, 1947 August 11-15; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Sixteenth Convention: Information Brochure, 1952; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Sixteenth Convention: Offical List of Delegates, 1952 October 13; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - [NOTE: ITEM IS MISSING] Sixteenth Convention Proceedings, 1952 October 13-17; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Sixteenth Convention: Reports, 1952 October 13; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Sixteenth Convention: Souvenir, 1952 October 13-18; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Sixteenth Convention: Events and Information Program, Tour Guide, and Teamster Magazine, October 13-18, 1952; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Sixteenth Convention, Events and Information Program, 1952 October 13-18; Series 2 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Sixteenth Convention, El Camino Real, 1952 October 13-18; Series 2 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Sixteenth Convention Proceedings, 1952 October 13-17; Series 2 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Sixteenth Convention, What to Do, Where to Go, What to See in Los Angeles, 1952 October 13-18; Series 2 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Seventeenth Convention: Constitution, 1957 October 3; Series 2 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Seventeenth Convention: Official List of Delegates, 1957 September 30; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Seventeenth Convention: Official List of Delegates & Roll Call, September 30, 1957; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Seventeenth Convention Proceedings, 1957 September 30 - October 5; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Seventeenth Convention: Proposed Constitution, 1957 September 30; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Seventeenth Convention: Report of John F. English, 1957 September 30; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Seventeenth Convention: Report of General President, Dave Beck, September 30, 1957; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Seventeenth Convention, Miami Beach IBT Conference, Correspondence between Mayor Kenneth Oka, Chief of Police Michael Fox, Publicity Director Harold Gardner, Sheriff of Dade County Thomas Kelly, and the IBT, 1957 September; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Eighteenth Convention: Adopted Constitution, 1961 July 3; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Eighteenth Convention: Official List of Delegates, 1961 July 3; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Eighteenth Convention: Officer's Report, July 3, 1961; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Eighteenth Convention Proceedings, 1961 July 3-7; Series 2 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Eighteenth Convention: Proposed Constitution, 1961 July 3; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Nineteenth Convention: Adopted Constitution, 1966 July 4-7; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Nineteenth Convention: Agenda, 'All Star Revenue' & Airline Division Report, July 4-8, 1966; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Nineteenth Convention Proceedings, 1966 July 4-7; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Nineteenth Convention: Proceedings-Second, Third, and Fourth Days, July 5-7, 1966; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Nineteenth Convention: Officer's Report, July 4, 1966; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Nineteenth Convention, Official List of Delegates, 1966 July 4; Series 2 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Twentieth Convention: Adopted Constitution, 1971 July 5-8; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Twentieth Convention Proceedings, 1971 July 5-8; Series 2 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Twentieth Convention: Officer's Report and Teamsters Magazine, July 5-8, 1971; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Twenty-first Convention: Adopted Constitution, 1976 June 14-17; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Twenty-first Convention: Officers' Report, 1976 June 14; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Twenty-first Convention Proceedings, 1976 June 14-17; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Twenty-second Convention Proceedings, 1981 June 1-5; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Twenty-Second Convention: Proceedings-Fourth Day, June 4, 1981; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Twenty-second Convention: Proposed Constitution, 1981 June 1; Series 2 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Twenty-Second Convention: Official List of Delegates, June 1, 1981; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Twenty-Second Convention: Officer's Report, June 1-4, 1981; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Twenty-third Convention: Adopted Constitution, 1986 May 19-23; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Twenty-third Convention: Brochure, 1986 May 19-23; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Twenty-third Convention Proceedings, 1986 May 19-23; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Twenty-third Convention: Officer's Report, May 19, 1986; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Twenty-third Convention: Official List of Delegates & Proposed Constitution and By-Laws, May 19, 1986; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Twenty-Third Convention, Official List Delegates, 1986 May 19; Series 2 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Twenty-fourth Convention: Officers Report, 1991 June 24; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Twenty-Fourth Convention: Agenda, Official List of Delegates, & Officer's Report, June 24-28, 1991; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Twenty-fourth Convention Proceedings, 1991 June 24-28; Series 2 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - 24th Convention: Resolutions and Report of Committee on Rules, June 24, 1991; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - 24th Convention: Proposed Constitution & By-Laws, June 24, 1991; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - 24th Convention: Proceedings-First, Second, Third, Fourth, and Fifth Days, June 24-28, 1991; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - 25th Convention: Proposed Constitution & By-Laws, July 15-19, 1996; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - "Teamsters"-History Booklet, 1999; Series 2 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Twenty-Fifth Convention: Official List of Delegates, July 15, 1996; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Twenty-fifth Convention Proceedings, 1996 July 15-19; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Twenty-Fifth Convention: Proceedings-First and Second Days, July 15-16, 1996; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Twenty-Fifth Convention: Proceedings-Third, Fourth, and Fifth Days, July 17-19, 1996; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Twenty-sixth Convention Proceedings, June 25-29, 2001; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Twenty-Sixth Convention: Proposed Constitution, June 25-29, 2001; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Twenty-seventh Convention Proceedings, 2006 June 26-30; Series 2 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Twenty-Seventh Convention: Officer's Report, 2006; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Twenty-eighth Convention Proceedings, 2011 June 27 - July 1 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - 28th Convention: Appeals and Grievances Committee Report, 2011; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - 28th Convention: Diversity Committee Report, 2011; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - 28th Convention: Flyers, 2011; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - 28th Convention: Official List of Delegates, 2011; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - 28th Convention: Pension and Benefits Committee Report, 2011; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - 28th Convention: Proceedings [1/2], 2011; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - 28th Convention: Proceedings [2/2], 2011; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - 28th Convention: Proceedings-First & Second Days, June 27-26, 2011; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - 28th Convention: Proceedings-Third & Fourth Days, June 27-26, 2011; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - 28th Convention: Officer's Organizing Report, 2011; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - 28th Convention: Officer's Report, 2011; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - 28th Convention: Official List of Delegates, 2011; Series 2 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - 28th Convention: Proposed Constitution, 2011; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - 28th Convention: Resolutions Committee Report, 2011; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - 28th Convention: Rules Committee Report, 2011; Series 2 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Blank Certificates-'Credential to convention', 1912-1925; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - AFL-CIO, Teamsters International Convention-San Francisco, August, 1947; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - 1971 Convention Clippings-James Hoffa and Frank Fitzsimmons, Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - "Building Teamster Power: Final Report of the Blue Ribbon Commission on Teamster Finances", March 1, 2002; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Special Teamsters, AFL-CIO Convention: A Stenographic Record" by James P. Connor, April 30, 2002; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - "Teamsters Canada" Printout & Photocopies from 17th and 19th Convention Proceedings, April 2004; Series 2 (Box 18, Folder 8)